AMANDA LIM USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

amandalimux.com linkedin.com/in/amlimux (312) 613 9664 amandamlim86@gmail.com

OVERVIEW

User experience designer trained at U.C. Berkeley extension in UX/UI design. Strengths in creativity, teamwork and building projects from ideation to execution. A background in landscape architecture has lead me to craft a passion for solving complex problems through the combination of form and function; creating visually appealing yet usable spaces with a focus on user centered design.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Landscape Architecture Designer

Meeks Design Group (October 2013 - Present)

Project Lead for multifamily and senior housing developments, managing projects through concept, design and development of construction documents in a collaborative interdisciplinary team environment with a focus on functional user centered design

Brand Expert

Gap, Inc. (February 2013 - September 2014)

Visual merchandiser for Gap Top 100 store, collaborated with Brand Team to implement and maintain all in-store visual design and display directives based on corporate brand style guides while contributing to advertising, marketing and sales efforts of the store

Brand Manager

Altar'd State (September 2012 - February 2013)

Assistant Store Manager, executed all visual merchandising of sales floor and window displays, led and directed all activities required to achieve store goals, including sales objectives, customer service, human resource management and loss prevention, while driving employee and customer engagement



ACHIEVEMENTS

Website Redesign

Project Giving Kids (August 2021)

Worked in a 2 week sprint to produce a website redesign for a non-profit organization to provide a more streamline user experience, create a cohesive brand identity and enhance user retention



EDUCATION

UX | UI Design Certificate

UC Berkeley (May 2021 - October 2021)

BS Landscape Architecture

Purdue University (2004 - 2010)



Research & Analysis

User Research Plan & Interviewing, Empathy Mapping, Affinity Diagramming, Guerrilla & **Usability Testing**

Solution Design

Proto/User Persona Creation, Storyboarding and User Journey Mapping, Wireframing & Prototyping, User Flows, Visual Design

Computer Programs & Code

Figma, Miro, InVision, HTML/CSS



ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Computer Skills

AutoCAD, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

Personal Skills

Detail Oriented, Creative, Empathetic, Organized, Collaborative Team Player